<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>va7unx.space</title>
    <link>https://va7unx.space/</link>
    <description>Recent content on va7unx.space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:58:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://va7unx.space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened in February</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/what_happened_in_february_2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:58:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/what_happened_in_february_2021/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what I got up to in February 2021:
Polaris  Recorded and presented my talk on Polaris for PyCascades. It went pretty well, I think.  Machine learning/data science   Began Chapter 9 of the FastAI book. This is on tabular learning, which is really interesting; I think this is the sort of approach I&amp;rsquo;d want to take for loostmap, my attempt to predict HF propagation by looking at data from the Reverse Beacon Network (I picked that project name from a random name generator&amp;hellip;I really need something that makes more sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Apache and UTF8</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/fixing_apache_and_utf8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 13:42:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/fixing_apache_and_utf8/</guid>
      <description>A while back, I started having problems with the output of Venus, a planet-like aggregator I use to read a bunch of things. The symptoms were broken characters for things like apostrophes, quotes and so on &amp;ndash; which rendered the output nearly unusable. I dug into it, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t resolve the problem&amp;hellip;so I resorted to a bletcherous hack (cron job to copy the file to my laptop, and view it with file:///.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Happened in January</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/what-happened-in-january_2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 11:52:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/what-happened-in-january_2021/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list, for my own reference, of what I got up to in January. It&amp;rsquo;s heartening to see everything laid out, and realize that I&amp;rsquo;ve actually managed to get a fair bit done!
Hardware hacking   My father-in-law and I worked on getting the precipitation meter going for our weather station. It took a while, but we finally got it working. 🎉
  Some one-wire temperature sensors came in, and I was able to whip up a quick demo to make sure they worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Trail Cam</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/urban-trail-cam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 16:14:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/urban-trail-cam/</guid>
      <description>Last year, my father-in-law got a trail cam at my suggestion &amp;ndash; mainly to get pictures of the rats that were eating his compost. It worked:
I borrowed it a while back, and finally set it up today under our bird feeder to see what we could get. Not a bad haul! We got:
 Spotted towhees:   Dark-eyed juncos:   Black and grey squirrels:   A chickadee:  Not bad!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dishwasher Loading Critic</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/dishwasher-loading-critic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 21:52:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/dishwasher-loading-critic/</guid>
      <description>My project: critiquing your dishwasher loading technique using machine learning. A work in progress. You can find the repo here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Ai and Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/posts/fast-ai-and-pytorch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 15:28:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/posts/fast-ai-and-pytorch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in machine learning for a while now. Like a lot of things, my approach has been a bit scattered. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly learning how to get better at that, but I still tend to veer around.
A couple of months ago, I decided to take the Fast.ai course again. I had done a couple of lessons a year ago, but had not followed it up. This time around, I saw that they not only had a new version of the course, but a book as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://va7unx.space/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:38:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://va7unx.space/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just this guy, you know?
Interests and past hobbies:
 Linux Go, Python, Lisp Arduinos Amateur radio SPAAAAAAAACE Machine learning  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>